{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","sessionId":"1","userId":0,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:29:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:29:47 GMT"}
{"type":"activityDidMount","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:29:50 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:29:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>"},0],"startTime":1537799389137,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799403148},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:03 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:03 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[1,-14014],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:03 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the son of Donald<br>\nDonald is the father of Jennifer<br>\nDonald is the brother of Liam</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Jennifer?</p>"},0],"startTime":1537799397757,"answer":{"choice":"Donald"},"answerTime":1537799409290},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:09 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.125,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:09 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[0,-11535],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:09 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>"},1],"startTime":1537799405155,"answer":{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799415509},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[2,-24368],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>"},2],"startTime":1537799417513,"answer":{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799425042},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[3,-31898],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:25 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Liam","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Walter"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Susan is the mother of Kevin<br>\nLiam is the father of Walter<br>\nJerry is the brother of Kevin<br>\nWalter is the brother of Susan</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Jerry?</p>"},1],"startTime":1537799411296,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1537799433925},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.25,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[0,-34165],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:33 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>"},3],"startTime":1537799427045,"answer":{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799438160},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[4,-43014],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:38 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Dorothy","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Rose"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Iris is the mother of Dorothy<br>\nDorothy is the sister of Rose<br>\nRose is the mother of Bob<br>\nBob is the brother of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Dorothy</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Cynthia?</p>"},2],"startTime":1537799435930,"answer":{"choice":"Rose"},"answerTime":1537799455852},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.375,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[0,-54088],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:55 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Zed","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Kevin"},{"choice":"Richard"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Dorothy is the daughter of Zed<br>\nKevin is the brother of Dorothy<br>\nKevin is the husband of Elenna<br>\nManuel is the son of Elenna<br>\nDorothy is the mother of Richard<br>\nRichard is the brother of Jerry</p>\n<p>Who is the grandfather of Manuel?</p>"},3],"startTime":1537799457857,"answer":{"choice":"Richard"},"answerTime":1537799458325},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.5,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[0,-54556],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:58 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>"},4],"startTime":1537799440164,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799459613},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[5,-62463],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:30:59 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Donald"},{"choice":"Manuel"},{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Nestor is the son of Vivian<br>\nNelly is the daughter of Donald<br>\nLiam is the brother of Nelly<br>\nLiam is the husband of Vivian<br>\nCharles is the brother of Nelly<br>\nManuel is the brother of Grace<br>\nNelly is the mother of Manuel</p>\n<p>Who is the uncle of Nestor?</p>"},4],"startTime":1537799460336,"answer":{"choice":"Charles","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799461376},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.625,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[1,-55597],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:01 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>"},5],"startTime":1537799463378,"answer":{"choice":"Ferdinand"},"answerTime":1537799465393},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[1,-57612],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:05 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>"},6],"startTime":1537799467395,"answer":{"choice":"I don't know"},"answerTime":1537799475360},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[1,-65577],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:15 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>"},7],"startTime":1537799477366,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799478099},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[2,-66310],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"Pc3KxBHkGLsLdDhfJ","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:18 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Ferdinand"},{"choice":"Harold"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Ferdinand is the husband of Grace<br>\nAlbert is the son of Grace<br>\nFerdinand is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Harold<br>\nTom is the brother of Laura<br>\nHarold is the brother of Iris<br>\nLaura is the daughter of Dorothy<br>\nRichard is the son of Iris</p>\n<p>Who is the grandson of Laura?</p>"},5],"startTime":1537799461620,"answer":{"choice":"Richard","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799480416},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:20 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.75,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:20 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[6,-81260],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:20 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Iris"},{"choice":"Cynthia","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"Laura"},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Laura is the daughter of Iris<br>\nJerry is the husband of Cynthia<br>\nCharles is the son of Cynthia<br>\nJerry is the brother of Laura<br>\nLaura is the mother of Zed<br>\nPaul is the son of Vivian<br>\nTom is the brother of Donald<br>\nDonald is the brother of Laura<br>\nZed is the brother of Vivian</p>\n<p>Who is the aunt of Vivian?</p>"},6],"startTime":1537799482420,"answerTime":1537799512424},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":0.875,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[6,-111266],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:31:52 GMT"}
{"type":"answer","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","payload":{"curQuestion":[{"answers":[{"choice":"Petra"},{"choice":"Wendy"},{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},{"choice":"I don't know"}],"question":"<p>Petra is the mother of Walter<br>\nManuel is the son of Kevin<br>\nZed is the brother of Liam<br>\nPetra is the daughter of Ferdinand<br>\nHarold is the husband of Wendy<br>\nGrace is the wife of Ferdinand<br>\nJerry is the son of Wendy<br>\nHarold is the brother of Petra<br>\nLiam is the brother of Petra<br>\nWalter is the brother of Kevin</p>\n<p>Who is the mother of Liam?</p>"},7],"startTime":1537799514437,"answer":{"choice":"Grace","isCorrect":true},"answerTime":1537799527607},"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"progress","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":1,"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:32:07 GMT"}
{"type":"score","itemId":"","activityId":"cjmge1180000w01yw8ti9n2aq","value":[7,-124436],"sessionId":"1","userId":1,"instanceId":"qMfkLqEWcy7Wx3n3p","timestamp":"Mon, 24 Sep 2018 14:32:07 GMT"}
